A Guide to the Norfolk (Va.) Building Inspection Office Architectural Drawings and Plans, 1898-1980
Library of Virginia
- Proposed Addition to Mama Kayer's Bakery - Permit Number: 20482, Address: 1140 Kingwood Dr., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 12; Tag Number: 1970-020 (Box 47, Folder 695)
  Drawn by: Melvin M. Spence, A.I.A., Architect, 966 Norfolk Sq., Norfolk,Va.; Contractor: G. S. Thompson; Commissioned by: Mama Kayer's Bakery
- Addition to Dispatcher's Office, Southern Materials Co. - Permit Number: 21216, Address: 2125 Kimball Ter., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-110 (Box 47, Folder 696)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Southern Materials Co.
- Zayre Gasoline Facility - Permit Number: 21238, Address: 1720 Little Creek Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 9; Tag Number: 1970-112 (Box 47, Folder 697)
  Drawn by: Chewing, Britt, Hoggard, Lamm, and Gresham, Architects, Engineers, Planners, Virginia Beach, VA; Contractor: Carter Bell Corp.; Commissioned by: Zayre Corp.
- Geral G. Givens Warehouse - Permit Number: 21020, Address: 3501 Argonne Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1970-092 (Box 47, Folder 698)
  Drawn by: W. L. Hughes Construction Co., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: W. L. Hughes Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Gerald G. Givens
- Albemarle Building, Tidewater Executive Center - Permit Number: 21214, Address: 400 N. Center Dr., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 24; Tag Number: 1970-109 (Box 47, Folder 699)
  Drawn by: Abner C. Hopkins, R. W. Pearson, Jr., Associated Architects; Contractor: Koger Properties, Inc.; Commissioned by: Koger Properties, Inc.
- 6 or 8 One Bedroom Apartments for Keatley-LePage Realty - Permit Number: 21075, Address: 1500 Kerry Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-099 (Box 47, Folder 700)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: George A. LePage Realty Corp.; Commissioned by: George A. LePage
- New Office and Shop Building, Pacific Ordnance and Electronics - Permit Number: 21146, Address: 1300 Ingleside Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 17; Tag Number: 1970-102 (Box 47, Folder 701)
  Drawn by: Lindemann Construction Co., 600 W. 25th St., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Lindemann Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Pacific Ordnance and Electronics
- Oakmont North Townhouses, F. H. A. Project No. 051-55025-INV-R - Permit Number: 20589-20598, Address: Rosefield Dr. and Rosefield Ct., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 24; Tag Number: 1970-046 (Box 47, Folder 702)
  Drawn by: Tasso Katselas, Architect and Planning Consultant, Pittsburgh, PA; Dudley, Morrisette, Cederquist and Associates, Architects and Planners, Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Baycon Corp.; Commissioned by: Renewal, Inc.
- [Proposed Office Building] - Permit Number: 20842, Address: 6644 Virginia Beach Blvd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1970-079 (Box 48, Folder 703)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: C. R. Magliano; Commissioned by: Dr. Ben Ward
- Addition and Renovations to Ship's Cabin Restaurant - Permit Number: 21364, Address: 4110 E. Ocean View Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-118 (Box 48, Folder 704)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Joseph L. Hoggard; Commissioned by: Joseph L. Hoggard
- Laboratory, Mental Health, and Nursing Buildings for Norfolk, VA - Permit Number: 20989, Address: 401 Colley Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 22; Tag Number: 1970-090 (Box 48, Folder 705)
- [Addition to Office Building] - Permit Number: 20656, Address: 2468 E. Little Creek Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1970-053 (Box 48, Folder 706)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: John Woodward; Commissioned by: John Woodward
- H. Salt Authentic English-Take Home Fish and Chips Restaurant - Permit Number: 21121, Address: 816 E. Brambleton Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 14; Tag Number: 1970-100 (Box 48, Folder 707)
  Drawn by: Hart, Freeland and Roberts, Edmund K. Armistead, Architect, Nashville, TN; Contractor: Tru Build Construction Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Kentucky Fried Chicken Corp.
- Seabord Citizens National Bank Building, 14th Floor - Permit Number: 21061, Address: 5 Main Plaza East, 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: 1970-097 (Box 48, Folder 708)
  Drawn by: Vlastimil Koubek, A.I.A., Registered Architect, 1200 Seventeenth St. NW, Washington, DC; Contractor: C. Richard Wilton; Commissioned by: United Virginia Bank
- Alterations to Building - Permit Number: 15643, 15644, Address: 3918 Hampton Blvd., 1968, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1968-307 (Box 48, Folder 709)
  Drawn by: Konikoff and Kennedy, Architects, 905 W. 21st St., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Commercial Building Services, Inc.; Commissioned by: Dudley Cooper
- Norfolk Jewish Community Center - Permit Number: 20930, Address: 331 North Shore Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-084 (Box 48, Folder 710)
  Drawn by: Konikoff and Kennedy, Architects, 905 W. 21st St., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Conrad Bros. Inc.; Commissioned by: Norfolk Jewish Community Center
- Additions and Alterations, Bruce-Flournoy Ford - Permit Number: 20530, Address: 7520 N. Military Hwy., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-036 (Box 48, Folder 711)
  Drawn by: Edwin B. Small, Structural Engineer; Contractor: George Jensen; Commissioned by: Flournoy and Bruce Corp.
- Seaboard Citizens Naitonal Bank Building, 13th Floor - Permit Number: 21060, Address: 5 Main Plaza East, 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-096 (Box 48, Folder 712)
  Drawn by: Vlastimil Koubek, A.I.A., Registered Architect, 1200 Seventeenth St. NW, Washington, DC; Contractor: F. Richard Wilton; Commissioned by: United Virginia Bank
- [Addition to] Sanctuary Building, Fairmount Park Free-Will Baptist Church - Permit Number: 21377, Address: 3240 Brest Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 10; Tag Number: 1970-121 (Box 48, Folder 713)
  Drawn by: Carlton T. Goodwin, A.I.A., Architect, One Tidewater Executive Center, Norfolk, VA; Commissioned by: Fairmount Park Free Will Baptist Church
- Alterations and Additions to Westminster Baptist Church - Permit Number: 20511, Address: 3412 Westminster Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-033 (Box 48, Folder 714)
  Drawn by: Chewing, Goodwin, and Hoggard, Architects, Engineers, Urban Planners, Virginia Beach and Hampton, VA; Contractor: L. J. Hoy, Inc.; Commissioned by: R. O. Hux, Sr.
- [10 Family Apartment Building] - Permit Number: 20628, Address: 1720 E. Ocean View Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1970-050 (Box 48, Folder 715)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: James A. Murphy, Jr.; Commissioned by: James A. Murphy, Jr.
- [6 Family Apartment Building] - Permit Number: 21165, Address: 9636-9638 Ninth View St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1970-104 (Box 48, Folder 716)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: J. A. Murphy, Jr.; Commissioned by: Linroy Builders, Inc.
- Metal Storage Building, Wells-Drury Construction Co. for Ronald Linquist - Permit Number: 20755, Address: 5430 Azalea Garden Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-064 (Box 48, Folder 717)
  Drawn by: Kirby Building Systems, Inc., Houston, TX; Contractor: Wellsy-Drury Construction Co.; Commissioned by: R. Linquist
- [Gasoline Storage Tanks] - Permit Number: 22938, Address: 8201 Hampton Blvd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-259 (Box 48, Folder 718)
  Drawn by: A. Carl Schenck, Construction Management and Engineering Consultants, Norfolk, VA; Commissioned by: Humble Oil and Refining Co.
- New Showroom and Shop Building for Willoughby Bay Marina - Permit Number: 21196, Address: 1585 Ocean View Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-107 (Box 48, Folder 719)
  Drawn by: Gresham Metal Buildings Co., Inc., ARMCO Building Systems and Products, 1060 W. 26th St., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Gresham Metal Buildings Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Willoughby Bay Marina
- New Freezer Facility for Stewart Sandwiches, Inc. - Permit Number: 21317, Address: 5722 Curlew Dr., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1970-116 (Box 48, Folder 720)
  Drawn by: Lindemann Construction Co., 600 W. 25th St., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Lindemann Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Stewart Sandwiches, Inc.
- [Storage Shed] - Permit Number: 21211, Address: 900 Widgeon Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1970-108 (Box 48, Folder 721)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Jack N. Powell
- [10 Family Apartment Building] - Permit Number: 21373, Address: 141 D. View Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-119 (Box 48, Folder 722)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Wilfred Bruner; Commissioned by: Wilfred Bruner
- [Sign for] Food Industries, Inc. [Kelly's Family Restaurants] - Permit Number: 20759, Address: 241 E. Little Creek Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-065 (Box 48, Folder 723)
  Drawn by: Talley Neon, 1908 Chamberlayne Ave., Richmond, VA; Frederick C. Weisensale, Structural Engineer; Contractor: Talley Neon; Commissioned by: Food Industries, Inc.
- Cardox High Pressure Fire Extinguishing System for Kitchen Ducts and Fryers, Norfolk General Hospital - Permit Number: 21225, Address: 600 Gresham Dr., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-111 (Box 48, Folder 724)
  Drawn by: Cardox, Division of Chemtron Corporation, Fire Systems Engineering; Contractor: Harry M. Brown; Commissioned by: Norfolk General Hospital
- Canopy Addition and Bay Conversion - Permit Number: 20610, 20613, Address: 6110 N. Military Hwy., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-047 (Box 48, Folder 725)
  Drawn by: Shell Oil Company, Southern Marketing Region; Contractor: A. C. Clark Co.; Commissioned by: Shell Oil Co.
- [Signs for Carrol's] - Permit Number: 22577, 22578, Address: 3554 N. Military Hwy., 1970, Media: Daizo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-218 (Box 48, Folder 726)
  Drawn by: Talley Neon and Advertising Co., Designers, Fabricators, Erectors, 1908 Chamberlayne Ave., Richmond; 3300 Cromwell Rd., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Talley Neon; Commissioned by: Carrol's
- [Signs for First Virginia Bank] - Permit Number: 20410, 20411, 20412, Address: 7350 Elm St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-006 (Box 48, Folder 727)
- A New Fuel Oil Tank Installation - Permit Number: 21148, Address: 2001 Church St., 1970, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1970-103 (Box 48, Folder 728)
  Drawn by: E. T. Gresham Co., Inc., Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: E. T. Gresham Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Sunlight Laundry and Dry Cleaners
- [Signs for Virginia National Bank] - Permit Number: 22742, Address: 3719 Hampton Blvd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-237 (Box 49, Folder 729)
- [Sign for Kelly's Restaurant] - Permit Number: 20760, Address: 1119 N. Military Hwy., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-066 (Box 49, Folder 730)
- Addition to Building, Anchor Post Products, Inc. - Permit Number: 20569, Address: 6601 Virginia Beach Blvd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-043 (Box 49, Folder 731)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Anchor Post Products, Inc.; Commissioned by: Anchor Post Products, Inc.
- [Alterations to Restaurant] - Permit Number: 22913, Address: 2314 Alabama Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-255 (Box 49, Folder 732)
  Drawn by: Charles H. Thayer, Jr., Structural Engineer; Contractor: Harold Spilka; Commissioned by: H. B. Bratten
- Perry's Suburban Barber Shop, Mr. Kenneth Perry, Sr. - Permit Number: 20749, Address: 7510 Granby St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-062 (Box 49, Folder 733)
  Drawn by: Richard Bobby, Artist-Designer, 1915 Colonial Ave., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: L. J. Hoy, Inc.; Commissioned by: K. R. Perry
- Kentucky Fried Chicken Restaurant - Permit Number: 21122, Address: 802 E. Brambleton Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 8; Tag Number: 1970-101 (Box 49, Folder 734)
  Drawn by: Paul D. Woodward, Architect; Contractor: Tru Build Construction Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Kentucky Fried Chicken
- Camellia [Style] House - Permit Number: 22267, 22268, Address: 5800, 5808 Bradley Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 8; Tag Number: 1970-262 (Box 49, Folder 735)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Shoal Development Corp.; Commissioned by: Shoal Developemtn Corp.
- [Addition to Office and Garage] - Permit Number: 20871, Address: 1090 W. 35th St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-080 (Box 49, Folder 736)
  Drawn by: Hodey White; Contractor: Hodey B. White, Jr.; Commissioned by: Yellow Cab Co.
- [Sign for Carwash] - Permit Number: 20659, Address: 4126 Llewellyn Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-054 (Box 49, Folder 737)
  Drawn by: Lewis A. Rightmier and Associates, Architect, A.I.A., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Carter Bell Corp.; Commissioned by: Nevis Corp.
- [Alterations to H. Salt, Esq. Fish and Chips] - Permit Number: 20517, Address: 1529 E. Little Creek Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1970-034 (Box 49, Folder 738)
  Drawn by: Heath and Company, Electrical Advertising/Store Fronts, 3225 Lacy St., Los Angeles, CA; Contractor: Calhoun Sign Co.; Commissioned by: H. Salt Co.
- Duplex- 2 Bedroom Units - Permit Number: 20650, Address: 2503 Wyoming Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: None (Box 49, Folder 739)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Robert W. Friosh; Commissioned by: Al Paolilli
- Dover Court Apartments - Permit Number: 20453, Address: 843 Bancker Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-013 (Box 49, Folder 740)
- [4 Family Apartment Building] - Permit Number: 21361, Address: 2403 Sewells Point Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-117 (Box 49, Folder 741)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Floyd A. Lamm, Jr.; Commissioned by: Floyd A. Lamm, Jr.
- Two Story, 12 Unit, 1 Bedroom Apartments - Permit Number: 22904, Address: 1361 E. Ocean View Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1970-254 (Box 49, Folder 742)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: W. F. Thornton, Jr.; Commissioned by: W. F. Thornton, Jr.
- Renovations to Store Building [for Office] - Permit Number: 20464, Address: 402-412 Duke St. and 220, 226, 228 Freemason St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1970-016 (Box 49, Folder 743)
  Drawn by: McGaughy, Marshall, and McMillan, A Professional Association, Architects and Consulting Engineers, Norfolk, VA; Washington, DC; Rome, Italy; Commissioned by: McGaughy, Marshall, and McMillan
- [Fotomat Building] - Permit Number: 21259, Address: 8502 Chesapeake Blvd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1970-113 (Box 49, Folder 744)
  Drawn by: Fotomat Corp., 920 Kline Ave., La Jolla, CA; Contractor: E. R. Davis and Sons; Commissioned by: Fotomat Corp.
- [Superette Service Station] - Permit Number: 21268, Address: 230 E. Little Creek Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 10; Tag Number: 1970-114 (Box 49, Folder 745)
  Drawn by: B and M Corporation, P.O. Box I, Scheiever, LA; Contractor: Petroleum Engineering Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Rosso and Mastracco
- Manpower Skill Center Alterations, City Schools of Norfolk, VA - Permit Number: 20944, Address: 511 E. 20th St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1970-087 (Box 49, Folder 746)
  Drawn by: Wilson B. Dodson, II, A.I.A., Architect, 716 W. 20th St., Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: J. E. Weddle and Assoc., Inc.; Commissioned by: Leroy Margolius
- Warehouse Modifications - Permit Number: 20795, Address: 2709 Nevada Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-070 (Box 49, Folder 747)
  Drawn by: Joseph D. Floyd Corp.; Contractor: Joseph D. Floyd Corp.; Commissioned by: Joseph D. Floyd Corp.
- Burn Unit, 5th Floor, B-Wing, Norfolk General Hospital - Permit Number: 20636, Address: 600 Gresham Dr., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 8; Tag Number: 1970-052 (Box 49, Folder 748)
  Drawn by: Clarence W. Meakin, A.I.A., Architect, 1709 Colley Ave., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: E. T. Gresham Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Norfolk General Hospital
- Four Unit Apartment Building for Irvin Klavan - Permit Number: 20473, Address: 2529 Villa Cir., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: 1970-019 (Box 49, Folder 749)
  Drawn by: Keeling, Washington, Washington, and Associates, Architects and Engineers, Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Marsel Builders; Commissioned by: Irvin Klavan
- Frank Thomas Company, Wheat Building - Permit Number: 20892, Address: 3 Main Plaza East, 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-081 (Box 49, Folder 750)
  Drawn by: McGaughy, Marshall, and McMillan, A Professional Association, Architects and Consulting Engineers, Norfolk, VA; Washington, DC; Rome, Italy; Contractor: George O. Gratz, Inc.; Commissioned by: Frank Thomas
- Office for Drs. Schlosberg and Mallick - Permit Number: 22746, Address: Bldg. G-12 Military Circle Mall, 1970, Media: Daizo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-239 (Box 49, Folder 751)
  Drawn by: Dudley, Morrisette, Cederquist and Associates, A.I.A., Architects and Planners, Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Barr Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Schosberg and Mallick
- [Alterations to] Edgerton and Lea, Ltd., Store No. F-18 - Permit Number: 201444, Address: F-18 Military Circle Mall, 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 9; Tag Number: 1970-011 (Box 50, Folder 752)
  Drawn by: Toombs, Amisano and Wells, Architects, 48 Cain St. N.E., Atlanta, GA; Contractor: Barr Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Military Square
- [Alterations to] Variety Records, Store No. F-15 - Permit Number: 20498, Address: F-15 Military Circle Mall, 1970, Media: Daizo prints; Sheets: 9; Tag Number: 1970-026 (Box 50, Folder 753)
- [Alterations to] Rowe and Long, Inc., Store No. F-13 - Permit Number: 20804, Address: F-13 Military Circle Mall, 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1970-074 (Box 50, Folder 754)
  Drawn by: Toombs, Amisano and Wells, Architects, 48 Cain St. N.E., Atlanta, GA; Contractor: Robert R. Marquis, Inc.; Commissioned by: Rowe and Long, Inc.
- [Alterations to] Virginia National Bank, Store No. G-1 - Permit Number: 20461, Address: G-1 Military Circle Mall, 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1970-015 (Box 50, Folder 755)
  Drawn by: Toombs, Amisano and Wells, Architects, 48 Cain St. N.E., Atlanta, GA; Contractor: W. A. Hall and Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Military Square, Inc.
- [Alterations to] House of Nine, Store No. F-14 - Permit Number: 20735, Address: F-14 Military Circle Mall, 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 10; Tag Number: 1970-059 (Box 50, Folder 756)
  Drawn by: Toombs, Amisano and Wells, Architects, 48 Cain St. N.E., Atlanta, GA; Contractor: Goodman Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Military Square, Inc.
- [Alterations to] Docktor Pet Center, Store No. TG-5 - Permit Number: 20499, Address: TG-5 Military Circle Mall, 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1970-027 (Box 50, Folder 757)
- [Alterations to] Price's, Inc. - Permit Number: 20803, Address: G-7 Military Circle Mall, 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1970-073 (Box 50, Folder 758)
  Drawn by: Toombs, Amisano and Wells, Architects, 48 Cain St. N.E., Atlanta, GA; Contractor: Robert R. Marquis, Inc.; Commissioned by: Price's, Inc.
- Chess King, Store No. K-6 - Permit Number: 21191, Address: K-6 Military Circle Mall, 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-106 (Box 50, Folder 759)
  Drawn by: Bernard H. Lepselter, P. E., Consulting Engineers, 410 E. 62nd St., New York, NY; Contractor: Turner Busch, Inc.; Commissioned by: Chess King
- [Alterations to] French Cafe, Store No. F-6 - Permit Number: 20501, Address: F-6 Military Circle Mall, 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1970-029 (Box 50, Folder 760)
- [Alterations to] The Singer Co., Store No. G-3 - Permit Number: 21435, Address: G-3 Military Circle Mall, 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-127 (Box 50, Folder 761)
  Drawn by: Bernard H. Lepselter, P. E., Consulting Engineers, 410 E. 62nd St., New York, NY; Commissioned by: Military Square, Inc.
- [Alteration to] Norfolk Federal Savings and Loan, Store No. F-19 - Permit Number: 21456, Address: F-19 Military Circle Mall, 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1970-129 (Box 50, Folder 762)
  Drawn by: Toombs, Amisano and Wells, Architects, 48 Cain St. N.E., Atlanta, GA; Contractor: L. J. Hoy, Inc.; Commissioned by: Military Square, Inc.
- [Alterations to] Merle Norman Cosmetics, Store No. TK-8 - Permit Number: 23715, Address: TK-8 Military Circle Mall, 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-342 (Box 50, Folder 763)
  Drawn by: Toombs, Amisano and Wells, Architects, 48 Cain St. N.E., Atlanta, GA; Contractor: Barr Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Merle Norman
- [Alteration to] Mary Perkins, Store No. F-17 - Permit Number: 21046, Address: F-17 Military Circle Mall, 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1970-094 (Box 50, Folder 764)
  Drawn by: Toombs, Amisano and Wells, Architects, 48 Cain St. N.E., Atlanta, GA; Contractor: Rorrer Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Military Square, Inc.
- [Alterations to] Rose Hall, Store No. G-6 - Permit Number: 20497, Address: G-6 Military Circle Mall, 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 19; Tag Number: 1970-025 (Box 50, Folder 765)
- [Private Club] - Permit Number: 22754, Address: 721 E. 29th St., 1970, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-241 (Box 51, Folder 766)
  Drawn by: Alex. O. Ferebee, Architect; Commissioned by: Howard Davis
- [Sign for Service Station] - Permit Number: 20625, Address: 649 Newtown Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-049 (Box 51, Folder 767)
  Drawn by: Gulf Oil Corporation, Southern Region, Engineering and Construction, Atlanta, GA; Contractor: A. L. Cline and Son Inc.; Commissioned by: Gulf Oil Corp.
- [Alterations to Store], Walden Book Store - Permit Number: 21163, Address: J-5 Military Cir., 1970, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1970-105 (Box 51, Folder 768)
- [Alterations to] Kinney Shoes, Store F-4 - Permit Number: 20798, Address: F-4 Military Cir., 1970, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1970-072 (Box 51, Folder 769)
  Drawn by: Toombs, Amisano and Wells, Architects, 48 Cain St. N.E., Atlanta, GA; Contractor: Barr Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Military Squre, Inc.
- [Alterations to] Fanny Farmer Candy Shop, Store J-1 - Permit Number: 20796, Address: J-1 Military Cir., 1970, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-067 (Box 51, Folder 770)
- [Alterations to] Zale Jewlery Store, Store K-1 - Permit Number: 20485, Address: K-1 Military Cir., 1970, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 9; Tag Number: 1970-022 (Box 51, Folder 771)
  Drawn by: Toombs, Amisano and Wells, Architects, 48 Cain St. N.E., Atlanta, GA; Contractor: Robert R. Marquis, Inc.; Commissioned by: Military Square, Inc.
- [Alterations to] Buddy Dale Hats, Store F-12 - Permit Number: 20797, Address: F-12 Military Cir., 1970, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-071 (Box 51, Folder 772)
- [Alterations to] Taylor Burgess Hair Styling Salon, Inc., Store K-2 - Permit Number: 20792, Address: K-2 Military Cir., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1970-068 (Box 51, Folder 773)
  Drawn by: Toombs, Amisano and Wells, Architects, 48 Cain St. N.E., Atlanta, GA; Contractor: Meredith Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Military Square, Inc.
- [Alterations to] Thom McAn, Store G-2 - Permit Number: 20521, Address: G-2 Military Cir., 1970, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: 1970-035 (Box 51, Folder 774)